<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Architect Expanded - Fences (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.ArchitectExpandedFences</packageId>
  <author>Nif</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/ArchitectExpandedFences</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
    <li>1.3</li>
    <li>1.4</li>
    <li>1.5</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>Mlie.Toolbox</packageId>
      <displayName>Toolbox</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2576079360</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/rmipa606/Toolbox/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
    <li>Mlie.Toolbox</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]
Update of Nifs mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2050680665

- Did not add the isFence attribute as it causes issues with fences that are impassable
- There is a reworked version of this mod [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2546954423]here[/url] that uses the vanilla fence code but does not have the option of tweaking the values using the Toolbox. 

[img]https://i.imgur.com/pufA0kM.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://dsc.gg/mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/ArchitectExpandedFences][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/Be8E2qJ.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/Z4GOv8H.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/K2IR5XG.png[/img]
A bit of misleading info on Cover percent. They're all based on fillPercent that has a range of 0-1 that I simply modified into 1-100%. Walls have a fillPercent of 1 or 100% in this case. However, since Rimworld does things differently for any fillPercent above 0.99 (99%), anything above it defaults back to 75%. In other words, there is no such thing as 100% cover. They are all supposedly 75%; the same as walls. Sorry for any confusion regarding Cover. The other fences below 100% should be accurate though.

[b]LAST EDIT:
I'm taking an indefinite hiatus as I'm getting more busier with life, especially college. You are free to modify and post the mod. Thank you for the support![/b]


[img]https://i.imgur.com/zfohC3m.png[/img]
An Architect Expanded mod that provides 8 types of fences that blends nicely with the vanilla aesthetic. All of which can be used as defense cover and can be easily modified with the mod settings, along with other options.

Description of each modifiable property of fences or gates can be found at the "Home" tab of the ToolBox settings: Mod Settings  ToolBox  Home. Another guide can be found at the [url=https://github.com/Nif-kun/ToolBox/wiki/User-Guide]ToolBox Wiki.[/url]


[img]https://i.imgur.com/FxzMqJw.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/LRaZs7b.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/7wedrea.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/LYz2uOw.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/USKR6rG.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/PEk2XvU.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/T22jZ1N.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/FEpo8B1.png[/img]
[img]https://i.imgur.com/ZR663zc.png[/img]


[img]https://i.imgur.com/66QlElQ.png[/img]
»Minor Update (v1.3.5.1) [08/11/20]
-Added 1.2 in supported versions.

»Bug Patch (v1.3.5.0) [05/06/20]
-Fixed: GenSpawn.SpawningWipes() and GenConstruct.CanPlaceBlueprintOver() patch of [AE] Fences. It broke the functionality of the Replace Stuff mod.

»Bug Patch (v1.3.4.0) [05/05/20]
-Fixed: GenSpawn.SpawningWipes() returning a null exception, causing floors to be unbuildable.

»Minor Update (v1.3.3.0) [04/21/20]
-Fence gate blueprints are now placable over fences, instead of removing the fences first and building the gate.

Note: As much as I don't like adding mod requirements due to possible future hiccups, Harmony is required to make this update possible. I'm fairly sure many of you have it already installed so this shouldn't be too much of a problem. If you haven't, here's a link to the mod: [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=2009463077]Harmony[/url].


[img]https://i.imgur.com/jVuN38U.png[/img]
»Blueprint for gates does not change appearance for vertical versions. It also does not update rotation instantly like doors. However, once built, it rotates immediately to align with the fences.
»This is not compatible with Vanilla Fences and even the Tab version. It still uses the same defName so it will overwrite which ever was loaded first.


[img]https://i.imgur.com/CBaAUnW.png[/img]
Q1: Save game compatible?
A1: Yes.

Q2: Removable from save game?
Q2: Yes. However, if you're still using ToolBox, an error will pop-up. Just open the ToolBox settings and close it to stop it from occurring. 

Q3: Will you be adding more fences?
A3: Yes, however, the other fences will act as an add-on. It will not be directly added in this mod.

Q4: Isn't this Vanilla Fences just retextured?
Q4: Well yes, but actually no. I've redone the whole settings and gates. Though I am sorry for taking a year to do all of those. I do things on my own pace.

Q5: Are the fences climbable?
Q5: Well no, but actually yes. By default, all fences cannot be stood or pass through. It can however be changed within the settings: Mod Settings  ToolBox  [AE] Fences

Q6: Can I use this on a save that previously used Vanilla Fences?
A6: You'll 100% get an error and all gates will disappear. The settings will not pass through, thus it will default to the current properties of the fences. The fences will still remain but will have significant damage. In other words, it's possible to transfer, but there will be drawbacks. 


[img]https://i.imgur.com/gemJ7gK.png[/img]
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=1884025115]Vanilla Expanded Collection[/url] - mods that stays true to Vanilla artstyle and concept.
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1579516669]Dub's Paint Shop[/url] - allows you to paint on buildings.
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1180719857][KV] Path Avoid[/url] - set places where colonist can and cannot walk on.
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1542284250]Greenworld Lite[/url] - dirt is less dirty and more grassy.
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2021234555]Gizmo Begone![/url] - allows you to hide the button of a building (gizmo).

[b]Patches: [/b]
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2050863037]Tab Patch[/url] - adds a "Fences" tab
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2051601925]Texture Patch[/url] - replaces the texture with the old ones from Vanilla Fences.


[img]https://i.imgur.com/lqddbVx.png[/img]
If you've uploaded a translation patch for this mod, leave down a link on the comment section. I'll gladly place a link here to your patch.

[b]German:[/b]
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/profiles/76561198033755089/]Erdnussbrot[/url]
[b]Russian (incomplete):[/b]
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/romwald]Romwald [BY][/url]
[b]Portuguese:[/b]
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/bambino-]Bambinoff[/url]
[b]Portuguese Brazilian:[/b]
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/bambino-]Bambinoff[/url]
[b]Chinese:[/b]
»[url=https://steamcommunity.com/id/361120441]阿寻[/url] = [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2050680665]workshop mod[/url]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/wCH6iiv.png[/img]
»Rimworld is owned by Tynan Sylvester.
»Art and Code used for the mod are created by me, Nif.


[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] or the standalone [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2873415404]Uploader[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[*] Use [url=https://github.com/RimSort/RimSort/releases/latest]RimSort[/url] to sort your mods
[/list]

[url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/changelog/2576081324][img]https://img.shields.io/github/v/release/emipa606/ArchitectExpandedFences?label=latest%20version&amp;style=plastic&amp;color=9f1111&amp;labelColor=black[/img][/url]</description>
  <modVersion IgnoreIfNoMatchingField="True">1.5.0</modVersion>
</ModMetaData>